#### Contact

816-262-1684 (Mobile) dslockha@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/patti-lockharta5b70023 (LinkedIn) gmail.com (Personal)

## Top Skills

Healthcare

**EMR** 

Maternity

#### Certifications

**NRP** 

ACLS

# Patti Lockhart

Registered Nurse at NursesRx

Saint Joseph, Missouri

# Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the wholesale industry. Skilled in Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), U.S. Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA), Clinical Monitoring, Healthcare Information Technology (HIT), and Neonatal Nursing. Strong healthcare services professional with a MS focused in adult and Women's tract from UMKC.

# Experience

NursesRx Registered Nurse August 2017 - Present (2 years 11 months)

Loyal Source Government Services
Travel Registered Nurse
October 2016 - Present (3 years 9 months)

Travel Nurses Across America (TNAA) Travel RN 2017 - Present (3 years) Little Rock, AR

RN in L&D, M/B and NSY

Quest
L&D -- OB RN
September 2015 - Present (4 years 10 months)
Travel nurse

Supplemental Health Care RN, areas of experience, L&D, NN, PP November 2014 - August 2015 (10 months) Lenexa, KS

complete care of normal and high risk OB patients during their hospital stay.

#### **KUMC**

L&D nurse

April 2012 - January 2015 (2 years 10 months)

#### Providence Medical Center

RN

2011 - January 2014 (3 years)

Kansas City, Missouri Area

L&D

### **Favorite Healthcare Staffing**

RN

January 2003 - 2012 (9 years)

### **Cerner Corporation**

sr. analyst

February 2005 - October 2010 (5 years 9 months)

#### Quintiles

Clinical Research Nurse

2008 - 2010 (2 years)

#### **NKCH**

staff RN in L&D

1996 - 2005 (9 years)

### St. Luke's Northland Hospital

L&D, PP registered nurse

February 1996 - October 1999 (3 years 9 months)

Barry Road, NKC

# Education

**UMKC** 

MS, adult and Women's tract · (1985 - 1991)

Truman

BSN, BS in Nursing, minor in Psychology · (1974 - 1978)